<?xml version="1.0"?><!DOCTYPE rss PUBLIC "-//Netscape Communications//DTD RSS 0.91//EN" "http://my.netscape.com/publish/formats/rss-0.91.dtd"><rss version="0.91">   <channel> <title>openEHR</title>     <link>http://www.openehr.org/new-ws/site/home.html</link>     <description></description>     <language>en-us</language><item>    <title>Board statement on CKM</title>    <link>http://www.openehr.org/new-ws/site/news_events/news/news5.php</link>    <description>What is Clinical Knowledge Manager? The Clinical Knowledge Manager (CKM) application is used by the openEHR Foundation to provide governance of archetypes, templates and terminology reference sets, and to facilitate discussions and communication about these assets within the openEHR community.</description></item>	 	 <item>    <title>Brazil re-affirms commitement to openEHR</title>    <link>http://www.openehr.org/new-ws/site/news_events/news/news4.php</link>    <description>As part of operationalising chapter III of the government decree (Nº 2.073, DE 31 DE AGOSTO DE 2011), a national EHR Workshop was held aimed at defining methods and standards to be used in the Brazilian EHR Project (RES-National). The conclusions were largely underpinned by openEHR.</description></item>	 <item>    <title>Interim board announces new openEHR Program groups</title>    <link>http://www.openehr.org/new-ws/site/news_events/news/news3.php</link>    <description>The interim board has now established 4 programs: Specifications, Software, Clinical Modelling and Localisation. Each Program has a Committee which will grow to up to 9 members and a list of Qualified Members to support each committee. Each group is beginning to work on the appropriate processes to support their activities.</description></item><item>	<title>CIMI forum - 5th meeting San Antionio</title>    <link>http://www.openehr.org/new-ws/site/news_events/news/news2.php</link>    <description>CIMI held its 5th group meeting in San Antonio from January 12 – 14, 2012. Over 35 people attended in person with an additional 5 participants attending via WebEx.</description></item>   </channel></rss>